[KAI]
I mean, yeah.
I talked to you that night.
But that was just
the springboard.
You're the one
who took it from there
and actually made the jump.
Don't keep letting your
old self drag you down.
Be a stone.
But be a gemstone.
[gasps]
♪
[sighs]
[UKA]
I'm sweating.
My back's on fire.
[indistinct chatter]
I'd be down to meet up
after class, cool?
-It's seat switching day!
-[gasps]
-[TONBO] Here we go!
-[MARIN] 'Bout time.
Now, draw your lot.
[UKA] Wait, hold on.
We're moving?
-I hope we'll still be close!
-[UKA] Already?
But why?
It's too soon!
There are things
I need to say to Endou!
[KAI]
You can want more.
Be a little greedy.
And as for everybody
who gave you a hard time?
Know that you're
better than them.
[gasps]
[sighs]
Hey, Endou?
I really hope
you'll be friends with me!
Uh...
[gasps]
[UKA] Did I mess up?
Wait, what do ya mean?
Were we not friends already?
[gasps]
-[whimpering]
-Huh?
[gasps]
I thought we were!
That's how I saw you!
-Am I wrong?
-I don't think so.
Huh?
Oh! Got it.
[AYUMI] You're just the kinda
girl who needs to hear
these things out loud.
[chuckles] Ha!
You're stuck with me!
♪
Screw last names!
We're friends!
-So, Uka, call me Ayumi...
-[UKA] Great things
-keep happening to me.
-...from here on out, okay?
How am I so lucky?
[SEKI]
C'mon, ladies.
Save the flirting for after
you've drawn your lots.
[AYUMI]
Okay!
[UKA]
Oh, right!
[MIRU]
Yo, Seto, what'd ya get?
-Six.
-Hm?
I'm three.
And seat three is...
[AYUMI]
Oh.
[both groaning]
[Ayumi whimpering]
[Uka whimpering]
[gasps]
Hey, Ayumi?
[UKA] Would you mind
switching seats with me?
-[Ayumi whimpering]
-[UKA] I pulled number 15!
-It's right next to Seto!
-[gasps]
[AYUMI] Was I seriously
being that obvious about it?
[UKA] I kinda thought
you two were already
going out together.
[AYUMI]
Kinda just a one-way thing.
You don't need to do that.
Really, I'll be okay!
[sighs]
No!
I wanna trade so I can sit
close to the teacher!
That's it!
[UKA]
I'm seeing miracles everywhere.
Can we?
-[UKA] For me...and her.
-[Ayumi sighs]
Oh, thank you.
[UKA]
For all of us.
♪
[sighs]
Yo, looks like
we're neighbors! Nice!
[UKA]
This one might've been
for my own
satisfaction, though.
-[gasps]
-[TOMOYA] Well...
I guess I'll be
right next to you.
Ah?
Lucky day!
[TONBO]
Oof, RIP to your seat, Kai!
[MIRU] No way you'll get
to sleep up there!
[Miru and Tonbo laughs]
-Huh?
-[TONBO] Right.
[MIRU]
Well, he can sleep anywhere.
[UKA] No way,
how did this happen?
You're up here too?
[UKA]
Things keep getting better.
Just when I think
my new world is full of light,
it sparkles even brighter.
-Uhh.
-Ah?
[laughs]
Don't see
what's so funny about this.
[birds chirping]
-[UKA]Hey, Ayumi, good morning!
-[AYUMI] Huh?
Good morning, Uka!
-Bye!
-[both gasping]
[AYUMI]
I figured she had more to say.
Was that it?
Did I miss something?
[AYUMI]
It's Uka, she's so funny!
[laughs]
-[ASUMI] Whatever.
-[UKA] Was that weird?
[AYUMI]
You're killing me.
[UKA] Yesterday,
I made a friend for the
-first time in my life. -Let's
talk about the trip tomorrow!
[ABE]
All the details are already
-in your guides...
-[UKA] And then,
-we had to change seats.
-...but make sure you wear
a uniform or gym clothes.
[ABE] Your footwear doesn't
need to abide our dress code,
though I would recommend
comfortable sneakers.
[UKA] It isn't safe for me
to look left or right.
[ABE]...no matter
how many times I say it...
[UKA]
Especially not right.
Wait, did I forget
to do anything today?
What if my hair's
totally messy?
What if there's
something on my face?
-What if there's lint on my
blazer? -Not my problem.
Leave me alone.
You can switch seats
if you'd prefer, Ishimori.
-[UKA] Oh! No!
-Ah?
-[UKA] Uh!
-No sweat, she's gonna be fine.
[gasps]
Uh, yeah! I'm fine!
Thanks for the offer, though.
-[ABE] You're sure?
-Yes.
[UKA]
Why ask?
Yo, you goin' out
with Ishimori?
[gasps]
No, he's not--
[KAI]
'Course not.
She's got no social skills.
I'm helping.
Like we can't
already tell, man.
Just a joke.
Your jokes suck.
Well, I know Kai's type,
and Ishimori's the furthest
thing you could find from it.
[UKA]
Come to think of it,
I know nothing
about his history.
Has he dated before?
-What kind of girl is his type?
-[TONBO] Don't be
-such a buzzkill, dude!
-Lay off! -[UKA] Though there's
more than just his love life.
I barely know
anything about him.
But now that we sit
next to each other,
I have my chance.
[UKA]
I can learn more.
[speaking in French]
[UKA]
He's good at pen-twirling.
[speaking in French]
[UKA] I can't believe
I actually sit next to him.
[speaking in French]
Ah. Here.
Thanks.
[speaking in French]
[KAI]
That sheet's torn.
-She needs a new one.
-Oh.
[speaking in French]
-[gasps]
-Let's fix that.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Uh, thank you!
[speaking in French]
[whimpering]
♪
[MIZOGUCHI] All right, kids,
open up to page 23.
Is anybody able
to answer this one?
[UKA]
He's asleep.
He even managed
from the front row.
Oh, here we go.
[TONBO]
Teach with the wind up.
-And the pitch!
-[indistinct chatter]
How'd he manage to do that
without even looking?
[whimpering]
Hey, don't clap
with them, Ishimori.
[chuckles]
Figured she would be lame.
But is the new girl
actually on our side?
I thought so too!
[AYAKA] She seems like the
type who'd look down
-on class clowns.
-[UKA] Oh, no.
-But maybe we misjudged her
there. -Is that how I come off?
-[KAI] You had her mixed up.
-Huh?
You're just seeing
the mask she wears.
If you get to know her, yeah.
You'll realize
she's actually pretty cool.
[Uka gasps]
Yeah?
I'm so down!
What's good, Ishimori?
[UKA]
What's...good?
[laughing]
Wait, what?
[laughs]
Why'd you bow?
Help.
What's the way you're
supposed to respond to that?
No one's ever said something
like that to me before!
Just say, "What's good"
back to her.
-Uh. Oh.
-What's good!
Uh, what's good, thank you!
[laughing]
Yeah!
[Kai laugh]
-Hey!
-Kai.
You really shouldn't tease
Ishimori as much as you do.
-[UKA] Wait, what's happening?
-[KAI] No, I promise I'm not.
[UKA]
He's teasing me?
[KAI]
That's good enough for now.
Make sure to pace yourself.
[indistinct chatter]
Now that they know
I think you're cool,
you'd better not let me down.
-[sighs]
-[KAI] I'll keep my eye on you.
[UKA]
It's magic.
[KAI] Think you can make
a hundred friends?
[UKA]
I will.
[KAI]
Well, let's see it.
[UKA]
This seat is magical.
-Wanna meet up by the park?
-Yeah, I can help you!
If you don't make me
wait for you!
[UKA]
I need to give back his hat.
[TONBO]
Uh-oh.
Looks like Kai disappeared.
-He was just here, though!
-[MIRU] Again?
[MIRU] So weird
how he vanishes sometimes.
I wonder where he went.
-Guess we gotta go find out!
-[UKA] Oh, he does that?
[UKA]
Okay.
That's another thing
I know about him, now.
Maybe I should try
looking for him, too.
[indistinct chatter]
♪
It doesn't feel like
he's going to make it easy.
You know,
not many people come here.
♪
[footfall]
Huh?
The storage room.
♪
Is there anyone here?
Doesn't look like it.
[gasps]
[gasping]
♪
[groaning]
Huh?
Hi.
Are you...okay?
You scared me!
I scared you?
A bunch of us
were looking for you!
[MARIN] Kai.
Where are you?
-[KAI] Quiet down.
-[MARIN] Kai!
-And shut the door behind you.
-[MARIN] Can you hear me?
-[UKA] Sure.
-[Marin groans]
Not over here.
So...
Uh...
they said you
disappear sometimes.
[UKA]
Do you always come here?
[sighs]
I've got a couple of places.
This one is for when
I need a quick nap.
[KAI]
Doesn't lunch make you sleepy?
♪
[UKA] Uh-oh.
Guess I interrupted his nap.
[KAI]
Why'd you bother checking here?
[UKA] I was looking
everywhere for you
and I saw that.
-Ugh!
-[UKA] Did I mess up?
First time that
anyone's found me.
Guess you win.
[UKA]
Was that a compliment?
[KAI]
That wasn't a compliment.
[UKA]
Oh.
I can only really imagine him
surrounded by people,
so this is a little surprising.
Well, I should get going.
[KAI]
What's up?
Aren't you here for a reason?
Ah!
♪
I wanted to return your hat.
So, here.
Oh, yeah.
Thanks so much
for lending it to me.
♪
-Did you wash it?
-Was that wrong?
Just something
you didn't need to do.
But still...
you're always wearing
that hat, aren't you?
[gasps]
[UKA] I figured maybe it meant
something important to you.
♪
-Not really.
-[gasps]
[KAI] I'm tired.
Wake me when it's time.
Oh, sure.
[UKA]
So, he doesn't mind me here.
♪
I keep on wondering.
Who is he?
He has so many faces,
and I wanted to see them all.
♪
Like, now, I'm curious.
But maybe I can't know
everything about him.
-Bed head.
-[gasps]
[KAI]
My hair's always a mess.
'Specially when I wake up.
Hence the hat.
I just got in the habit
of wearing them.
Ah!
[sighs]
[UKA]
Wait...is he blushing?
He is! Look!
[chuckles]
The all-too-cool Miura
is blushing!
[KAI]
What?
[UKA]
Honestly, it's kinda silly!
[chuckles]
Bed head!
Lay off.
[laughs]
I just can't stop! Sorry!
♪
-[UKA] Bed head.
-[KAI] Yeah.
[KAI]
Keep laughin'.
[UKA] For the first time,
he seems normal.
Like he's the same
as anyone else,
flaws and all.
[birds chirping]
Ah?
Kai!
[TONBO]
We looked all over for you!
Why?
[MARIN] C'mon now,
that's all you have to say?
Jeez, you never let us know
where you're running off to!
So, sneak somewhere
with Ishimori?
[UKA] Am I supposed
to speak up here?
Hey, why do you always
disappear on us?
I get sick of always
being around people.
-What?
-[Tonbo whimpering]
-No, this is terrible!
-So not us.
But Ishimori's okay, I guess?
[KAI] Yeah, she barely
counts as a person.
[gasps]
-Where'd he go?
-Ah?
You actually found him, right?
♪
[UKA]
I'm seeing new sides to him.
Learning everything I can.
And with each new thing,
I feel myself falling
even further in love.
It can't be stopped.
♪
My back, it's burning...
but it's fine.
♪
Any second now,
I could sprout wings and fly.
♪
[indistinct chatter]
[UKA]
Today, we have the school trip
to welcome new students.
♪
Oh, no.
[FEMALE STUDENT 3C]
Isn't that backpack too big?
Talk about overkill!
[UKA]
Looks like I messed up again.
You're lookin' good, girly!
I was thinking about
wearin' mine here, too!
-[gasps]
-[AYUMI] Now I wish
I'd actually
gone through with it!
Thank you,
oh, beautiful goddess.
Ah!
Hey, have you guys heard?
Apparently, there's a place
where you can look up
through the trees
and the branches
make a heart shape.
[both gasp]
Hear that?
You like that stuff!
-Yeah, I do.
-[FEMALE STUDENT 3F] Seriously?
Let's find it together.
Whoa! Is he?
Hold your horses.
He doesn't mean
anything by that.
You think he wants more?
Nope, he's just that dense!
[SATORU]
Hey, you two coming?
-[SATORU] Or what?
-[AYUMI] Yeah!
-Ah, best of luck.
-Thank you.
-[SATORU] Hm?
-[giggles]
[UKA] But hey,
she still gets to stand
next to the boy she likes.
Which is more than
I can say, right now.
-No way.
-C'mon,
don't be like that!
Why can't I?
[UKA]
Maybe he wants space.
Well, I am dressed
weird today,
so I can't blame him.
Ah?
And I just realized
I'm acting jealous.
It's not like I have the right
-to feel that way.
-Hey, what's up?
Just admiring the outfit.
[TOMOYA] You really
shouldn't make fun of her
like that, dude!
-[KAI] I'm not, though.
-Ah!
Just imagining her choice.
Bet she went back
and forth for hours.
[UKA] Every day is a new
range of experiences.
♪
Listen up! Stay together!
[TOGETHER]
'Kay!
[UKA] Some of the paths here
are steep.
-But we're on the flat route...
-Where'd she get the pamphlet?
[UKA]..so I could've
worn my uniform.
[MIKARIN] Hey, mountaineer!
You know the way?
[UKA]
"Mountaineer?" Huh?
Ah? Is that me?
Yeah, go right!
[chuckles]
It's a joke!
But still, good to know.
-[MIKARIN] Ishimori's so funny.
-[gasps]
[laughs]
Can you believe she said that?
Anyway, guess what Tamaki said!
[UKA]
Oh, I'm sorry.
I think I bumped
into something weird.
[FEMALE STUDENT 3H]
Like a freak?
Nah, just a stone.
[FEMALE STUDENT 3H]
Yeah, that is weird!
[FEMALE STUDENT 3G]
Right in our way!
[both laughs]
[UKA] There's so much I want
to do with my new class.
-[UKA] With my new friends!
-I got the hat!
♪
-Careful there, path's
getting slippery. -Whatever!
-Oh!
-[screams]
[gasps]
Oh, uh, thank you!
-So, clumsy.
-[SHIRAISHI] Are you okay?
-I'm just fine!
-[chuckles]
-Sure you're not flustered?
-Kai will never be an option!
[TAO]
Way too many rivals!
[SHIRAISHI]
Hey, relax.
Everyone goes
through a Kai phase.
[Tao groaning]
[SHIRAISHI] Though, of course,
nothing ever comes from it.
Only heartbreak.
But oh, well, who doesn't want
the forbidden fruit?
Plus, it's way too easy
to get lost in those eyes.
[MARIN]
What are you doing, Kai?
Come get your hat!
You can probably keep it.
Not like he has a shortage.
He's bought dozens
since junior high.
[TONBO] Actually, you remember
why he started wearing them?
[gasps]
I know!
[KAI]
Don't tell.
You're the only one
who knows my secret.
What was that?
You can't just walk away!
[gasps]
[UKA] But he'd
mentioned it so casually.
I figured it must've
been something
-everyone already knew.
-[wind whooshing]
So, why was he okay
-telling me something private?
-Whatever, I don't care.
[UKA]
Stop.
There's no special reason.
Don't read into it.
[MIKARIN] Look,
there's a perfect little spot
-to sit for lunch!
-[indistinct chatter]
[YASUSHI]
It's about time!
Hey, Uka, ya wanna
have lunch with me?
-Oh!
-Ah! Oh, sure!
[Ayumi groaning]
♪
[gasps]
Your lunch is so cute!
Cute girls even have
cute lunches.
[giggles]
Don't say that!
[AYUMI] I'm sure your lunch
is just as cute as...
-Didn't want meat?
-Huh?
Quick question.
You guys know why those girls
are staring up at the sky?
[SATORU] Yeah!
Sounds like a good-luck thing.
There's a break in the trees,
and apparently,
it makes the sky
look like a heart.
Yeah, good luck with that.
Kai, you think
it's dumb too, right?
-[gasps]
-[KAI] Not really.
-[TONBO] Quit lying!
-No, it's not a lie.
Pretty sure I remember
you going to a romantic spot
like that with a girl before.
[TONBO] What?
You're kidding me!
So not like you!
Satoru, learn how to shut up.
So, it's the truth?
[TONBO]
You can't do that stuff!
It's gonna kill
your whole vibe!
[KAI]
Like I care.
[UKA]
That makes sense.
Why wouldn't he?
It's Miura.
He's probably dated
more girls than I can imagine.
So, I can't freak out
over one secret.
It meant nothing.
He's not into me
or anything like that.
[indistinct chatter]
[UKA] Hold on,
the sign's pointing us
to the rougher path,
isn't that weird?
Should we really go this way?
But...
Something got you
freezing up again?
Looks like Mister Abe's
group went right.
Yeah, looks that way!
[TONBO]
So, Mountaineer, we good?
[UKA] I'm just
over-thinking things again.
We should go right.
HACHIMITSU
HIGH SCHOOL
[indistinct chatter]
♪
Has anyone else noticed
the path is steeper.
-Yeah.
-[thunder rumbling]
[all gasping]
[rain splattering]
[crying]
[KAMAKIRI]
Oh, c'mon!
[screams]
Quit running away!
But why?
It's coming down.
I get it, but don't run off!
We can't get split up!
What? Why make it sound
like such a big deal?
We know what path we're on,
so we're not lost or anything.
Back me up, Ishimori.
[UKA] [whimpering]
Uh, I think...
I think we're lost after all.
[ALL]
Hm?
[TOGETHER]
What?
[rain splattering]
TO BE CONTINUED